{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654327054","data":{"timestamp":" 947654327054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654329503","data":{"timestamp":" 947654329503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654332077","data":{"timestamp":" 947654332077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAAMKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654333772","data":{"timestamp":" 947654333772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654335348","data":{"timestamp":" 947654335348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654337140","data":{"timestamp":" 947654337139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654339821","data":{"timestamp":" 947654339821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yayeri mashuhuri anaamka mapema sana kila asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654342644","data":{"timestamp":" 947654342644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654344608","data":{"timestamp":" 947654344607"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654351528","data":{"timestamp":" 947654351528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654363327","data":{"timestamp":" 947654363327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654365415","data":{"timestamp":" 947654365415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654370680","data":{"timestamp":" 947654370680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654373105","data":{"timestamp":" 947654373105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" START_ANASHUKURU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654375460","data":{"timestamp":" 947654375460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHUKURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654378019","data":{"timestamp":" 947654378019"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654380029","data":{"timestamp":" 947654380029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654382382","data":{"timestamp":" 947654382382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anashukuru kwa usiku uliopita."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOPITA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654385294","data":{"timestamp":" 947654385294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654387662","data":{"timestamp":" 947654387662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654389648","data":{"timestamp":" 947654389648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654391848","data":{"timestamp":" 947654391848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654393658","data":{"timestamp":" 947654393658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654397113","data":{"timestamp":" 947654397113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654400918","data":{"timestamp":" 947654400917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATANDIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654403126","data":{"timestamp":" 947654403125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654405044","data":{"timestamp":" 947654405043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654407930","data":{"timestamp":" 947654407930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654410293","data":{"timestamp":" 947654410293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anatandika kitanda chake vizuri sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654413923","data":{"timestamp":" 947654413923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654417714","data":{"timestamp":" 947654417714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654421903","data":{"timestamp":" 947654421903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654424701","data":{"timestamp":" 947654424700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654426597","data":{"timestamp":" 947654426597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654429050","data":{"timestamp":" 947654429050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654430993","data":{"timestamp":" 947654430992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654431292","data":{"timestamp":" 947654431292"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWASALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654433563","data":{"timestamp":" 947654433563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654436395","data":{"timestamp":" 947654436395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654438441","data":{"timestamp":" 947654438441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654443638","data":{"timestamp":" 947654443638"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654445759","data":{"timestamp":" 947654445759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anawasalimu wazazi wake na mababu zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654448663","data":{"timestamp":" 947654448663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654452333","data":{"timestamp":" 947654452333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654454127","data":{"timestamp":" 947654454127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654456150","data":{"timestamp":" 947654456150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654462505","data":{"timestamp":" 947654462505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654472003","data":{"timestamp":" 947654472002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654474794","data":{"timestamp":" 947654474793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654476686","data":{"timestamp":" 947654476686"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654478613","data":{"timestamp":" 947654478613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654480463","data":{"timestamp":" 947654480463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654482808","data":{"timestamp":" 947654482808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654485654","data":{"timestamp":" 947654485654"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654487525","data":{"timestamp":" 947654487525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaosha uso wake kwa sabuni ya bluu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654493835","data":{"timestamp":" 947654493835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654495415","data":{"timestamp":" 947654495414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654497293","data":{"timestamp":" 947654497293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654499301","data":{"timestamp":" 947654499301"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654502515","data":{"timestamp":" 947654502515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654504831","data":{"timestamp":" 947654504830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654507730","data":{"timestamp":" 947654507730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654510009","data":{"timestamp":" 947654510009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654512399","data":{"timestamp":" 947654512399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654514153","data":{"timestamp":" 947654514153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654516993","data":{"timestamp":" 947654516992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654519183","data":{"timestamp":" 947654519183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSWAKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654520889","data":{"timestamp":" 947654520888"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654522430","data":{"timestamp":" 947654522430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654526398","data":{"timestamp":" 947654526397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anapiga mswaki meno yake na mswaki aina ya lughano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LUGHANO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654531260","data":{"timestamp":" 947654531260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654534262","data":{"timestamp":" 947654534262"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654538040","data":{"timestamp":" 947654538040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654540381","data":{"timestamp":" 947654540381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654542691","data":{"timestamp":" 947654542691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654545092","data":{"timestamp":" 947654545091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654548893","data":{"timestamp":" 947654548893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654550369","data":{"timestamp":" 947654550369"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654553203","data":{"timestamp":" 947654553203"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654555390","data":{"timestamp":" 947654555390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaoga kwa maji baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654561411","data":{"timestamp":" 947654561411"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654563219","data":{"timestamp":" 947654563219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654565510","data":{"timestamp":" 947654565510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654569529","data":{"timestamp":" 947654569528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654571442","data":{"timestamp":" 947654571442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654573905","data":{"timestamp":" 947654573905"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654575304","data":{"timestamp":" 947654575304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" ANAVAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654576135","data":{"timestamp":" 947654576134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654578045","data":{"timestamp":" 947654578045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654580309","data":{"timestamp":" 947654580308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654583542","data":{"timestamp":" 947654583542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654585665","data":{"timestamp":" 947654585664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654587440","data":{"timestamp":" 947654587440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654592561","data":{"timestamp":" 947654592560"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa sare ya shule ya rangi ya machungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654598836","data":{"timestamp":" 947654598836"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654600611","data":{"timestamp":" 947654600611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654603492","data":{"timestamp":" 947654603492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654605554","data":{"timestamp":" 947654605554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654607781","data":{"timestamp":" 947654607781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654610233","data":{"timestamp":" 947654610233"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654615357","data":{"timestamp":" 947654615356"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAVAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654617475","data":{"timestamp":" 947654617475"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654620424","data":{"timestamp":" 947654620424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654623565","data":{"timestamp":" 947654623564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anavaa viatu vyake vyeusi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYEUSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654626688","data":{"timestamp":" 947654626688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654628567","data":{"timestamp":" 947654628567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654630377","data":{"timestamp":" 947654630376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654632581","data":{"timestamp":" 947654632581"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654634286","data":{"timestamp":" 947654634286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654636599","data":{"timestamp":" 947654636599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654642714","data":{"timestamp":" 947654642714"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654644505","data":{"timestamp":" 947654644505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654646892","data":{"timestamp":" 947654646892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anafika shuleni mapema."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654649982","data":{"timestamp":" 947654649982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654651754","data":{"timestamp":" 947654651754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654653740","data":{"timestamp":" 947654653740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654655748","data":{"timestamp":" 947654655748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654658468","data":{"timestamp":" 947654658468"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654660689","data":{"timestamp":" 947654660688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654673688","data":{"timestamp":" 947654673688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAJIFUNZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654675991","data":{"timestamp":" 947654675991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654677528","data":{"timestamp":" 947654677528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654679920","data":{"timestamp":" 947654679919"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAYANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654683778","data":{"timestamp":" 947654683778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654685637","data":{"timestamp":" 947654685637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJAMII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654687242","data":{"timestamp":" 947654687242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654691205","data":{"timestamp":" 947654691204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anajifunza masomo ya sayansi ya kijamii na hesabu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HESABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654694817","data":{"timestamp":" 947654694817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654697084","data":{"timestamp":" 947654697084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654698962","data":{"timestamp":" 947654698962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654700876","data":{"timestamp":" 947654700876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654702735","data":{"timestamp":" 947654702735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654706333","data":{"timestamp":" 947654706332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654707975","data":{"timestamp":" 947654707974"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654708376","data":{"timestamp":" 947654708376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654710179","data":{"timestamp":" 947654710178"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654713677","data":{"timestamp":" 947654713676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OTAMENHAIBUGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654716780","data":{"timestamp":" 947654716780"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654719428","data":{"timestamp":" 947654719428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654722038","data":{"timestamp":" 947654722038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654728312","data":{"timestamp":" 947654728311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654730156","data":{"timestamp":" 947654730156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba na kucheza otamenhaibuga pamoja na mpira wa miguu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654735068","data":{"timestamp":" 947654735068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654736732","data":{"timestamp":" 947654736732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654738425","data":{"timestamp":" 947654738424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654741075","data":{"timestamp":" 947654741075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYERI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654742879","data":{"timestamp":" 947654742879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654745261","data":{"timestamp":" 947654745261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654747276","data":{"timestamp":" 947654747275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654747429","data":{"timestamp":" 947654747429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 80780757-09ef-4d74-9229-f34e342224b1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunajiuliza Kwa nini Yayeri ni mashuhuri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUHURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654758539","data":{"timestamp":" 947654758539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654758773","data":{"timestamp":" 947654758773"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654759750","data":{"timestamp":" 947654759749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654761033","data":{"timestamp":" 947654761033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654763978","data":{"timestamp":" 947654763977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654764829","data":{"timestamp":" 947654764829"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654765151","data":{"timestamp":" 947654765150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654766397","data":{"timestamp":" 947654766396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654769936","data":{"timestamp":" 947654769936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654770934","data":{"timestamp":" 947654770933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654771197","data":{"timestamp":" 947654771197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654772150","data":{"timestamp":" 947654772150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654775074","data":{"timestamp":" 947654775074"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654776119","data":{"timestamp":" 947654776118"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654776598","data":{"timestamp":" 947654776598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654781133","data":{"timestamp":" 947654781132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654781260","data":{"timestamp":" 947654781260"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 416b13db-c41a-47c5-9a06-5868105ab2f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654810180","data":{"timestamp":" 947654810180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654814107","data":{"timestamp":" 947654814107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654817652","data":{"timestamp":" 947654817652"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654823421","data":{"timestamp":" 947654823421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654828622","data":{"timestamp":" 947654828621"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654834347","data":{"timestamp":" 947654834347"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654838039","data":{"timestamp":" 947654838039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654841086","data":{"timestamp":" 947654841086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654845477","data":{"timestamp":" 947654845476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654849964","data":{"timestamp":" 947654849964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654853503","data":{"timestamp":" 947654853503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654858004","data":{"timestamp":" 947654858004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654862049","data":{"timestamp":" 947654862049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654871382","data":{"timestamp":" 947654871381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654874695","data":{"timestamp":" 947654874695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654877565","data":{"timestamp":" 947654877565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654882748","data":{"timestamp":" 947654882748"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654885820","data":{"timestamp":" 947654885820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654889992","data":{"timestamp":" 947654889992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654890976","data":{"timestamp":" 947654890975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654894983","data":{"timestamp":" 947654894983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654895225","data":{"timestamp":" 947654895225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654895891","data":{"timestamp":" 947654895890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654900285","data":{"timestamp":" 947654900285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654901110","data":{"timestamp":" 947654901109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654905484","data":{"timestamp":" 947654905483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654908331","data":{"timestamp":" 947654908331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654911286","data":{"timestamp":" 947654911286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654913522","data":{"timestamp":" 947654913522"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654915798","data":{"timestamp":" 947654915798"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654919524","data":{"timestamp":" 947654919524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654920293","data":{"timestamp":" 947654920293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654925571","data":{"timestamp":" 947654925571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654926952","data":{"timestamp":" 947654926952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654930310","data":{"timestamp":" 947654930310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654934377","data":{"timestamp":" 947654934377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654934931","data":{"timestamp":" 947654934930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654939598","data":{"timestamp":" 947654939597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654942061","data":{"timestamp":" 947654942061"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654944360","data":{"timestamp":" 947654944359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654947245","data":{"timestamp":" 947654947245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654947452","data":{"timestamp":" 947654947452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654951680","data":{"timestamp":" 947654951680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654952627","data":{"timestamp":" 947654952627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654956062","data":{"timestamp":" 947654956062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 69b25d2b-b73f-42bc-bab3-654779d7b6fd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654978185","data":{"timestamp":" 947654978185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654981129","data":{"timestamp":" 947654981129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654984819","data":{"timestamp":" 947654984819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654990781","data":{"timestamp":" 947654990781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947654994627","data":{"timestamp":" 947654994627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655001081","data":{"timestamp":" 947655001081"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655005943","data":{"timestamp":" 947655005943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655010535","data":{"timestamp":" 947655010535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655016565","data":{"timestamp":" 947655016565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655022505","data":{"timestamp":" 947655022505"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655026209","data":{"timestamp":" 947655026209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655030333","data":{"timestamp":" 947655030333"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655035506","data":{"timestamp":" 947655035506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655043477","data":{"timestamp":" 947655043477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655049429","data":{"timestamp":" 947655049429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655053314","data":{"timestamp":" 947655053314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655057011","data":{"timestamp":" 947655057011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655060304","data":{"timestamp":" 947655060304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655064569","data":{"timestamp":" 947655064568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655069778","data":{"timestamp":" 947655069777"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655079221","data":{"timestamp":" 947655079220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655089973","data":{"timestamp":" 947655089972"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655096036","data":{"timestamp":" 947655096035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655105669","data":{"timestamp":" 947655105668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655115151","data":{"timestamp":" 947655115150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655125901","data":{"timestamp":" 947655125900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655132091","data":{"timestamp":" 947655132091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655135416","data":{"timestamp":" 947655135415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655138944","data":{"timestamp":" 947655138943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655144125","data":{"timestamp":" 947655144124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655147287","data":{"timestamp":" 947655147287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655152676","data":{"timestamp":" 947655152676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655159424","data":{"timestamp":" 947655159424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655163493","data":{"timestamp":" 947655163493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655168302","data":{"timestamp":" 947655168302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655172934","data":{"timestamp":" 947655172934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655178624","data":{"timestamp":" 947655178624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655182870","data":{"timestamp":" 947655182870"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655193979","data":{"timestamp":" 947655193979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655198994","data":{"timestamp":" 947655198994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" -"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655200427","data":{"timestamp":" 947655200427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655204256","data":{"timestamp":" 947655204256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655207332","data":{"timestamp":" 947655207332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655211443","data":{"timestamp":" 947655211443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655218062","data":{"timestamp":" 947655218062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655222819","data":{"timestamp":" 947655222819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655226371","data":{"timestamp":" 947655226370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655230022","data":{"timestamp":" 947655230022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655233150","data":{"timestamp":" 947655233150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655238367","data":{"timestamp":" 947655238367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655247915","data":{"timestamp":" 947655247915"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655258655","data":{"timestamp":" 947655258655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655261980","data":{"timestamp":" 947655261980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655266749","data":{"timestamp":" 947655266749"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655272610","data":{"timestamp":" 947655272610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655278049","data":{"timestamp":" 947655278048"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655283664","data":{"timestamp":" 947655283664"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655286620","data":{"timestamp":" 947655286620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655291833","data":{"timestamp":" 947655291833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655301296","data":{"timestamp":" 947655301296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655311981","data":{"timestamp":" 947655311981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_3"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655319484","data":{"timestamp":" 947655319484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ."," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_4"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655329474","data":{"timestamp":" 947655329473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655339629","data":{"timestamp":" 947655339628"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655347784","data":{"timestamp":" 947655347783"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.dic.ltr:story_1.noerror.1.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655361274","data":{"timestamp":" 947655361272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655370142","data":{"timestamp":" 947655370141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 192a628d-5465-4cbd-836a-a7be1bf19692"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.dic.ltr_story_1.noerror.1.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655386222","data":{"timestamp":" 947655386222"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655388490","data":{"timestamp":" 947655388490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655390847","data":{"timestamp":" 947655390846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655393187","data":{"timestamp":" 947655393187"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHEREHE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655395034","data":{"timestamp":" 947655395034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655397282","data":{"timestamp":" 947655397282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulienda katika sherehe ya Dasara."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DASARA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655399849","data":{"timestamp":" 947655399849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655402040","data":{"timestamp":" 947655402040"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMNUNULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655403660","data":{"timestamp":" 947655403659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655405736","data":{"timestamp":" 947655405736"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655407407","data":{"timestamp":" 947655407407"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655409676","data":{"timestamp":" 947655409675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Papa alimnunulia Chintu miwani ya kupendeza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655411724","data":{"timestamp":" 947655411724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655414101","data":{"timestamp":" 947655414101"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALININUNULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655416733","data":{"timestamp":" 947655416732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655418757","data":{"timestamp":" 947655418757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655420688","data":{"timestamp":" 947655420688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655422725","data":{"timestamp":" 947655422725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655425532","data":{"timestamp":" 947655425532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655427913","data":{"timestamp":" 947655427913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYONG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655429719","data":{"timestamp":" 947655429719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655431617","data":{"timestamp":" 947655431617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alininunulia kofia ya rangi ya samawati iliyong'aa mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655433730","data":{"timestamp":" 947655433730"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655436428","data":{"timestamp":" 947655436427"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655438775","data":{"timestamp":" 947655438775"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto alipata peremende."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655441117","data":{"timestamp":" 947655441117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655446058","data":{"timestamp":" 947655446058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655447993","data":{"timestamp":" 947655447993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655449906","data":{"timestamp":" 947655449906"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655452403","data":{"timestamp":" 947655452402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655460681","data":{"timestamp":" 947655460681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655462613","data":{"timestamp":" 947655462613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tukiwa njiani kwenda nyumbani upepo mkali ulivuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIVUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655464929","data":{"timestamp":" 947655464929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655466871","data":{"timestamp":" 947655466871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655470555","data":{"timestamp":" 947655470555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655473772","data":{"timestamp":" 947655473772"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Uliipeperusha kofia yangu mbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655476108","data":{"timestamp":" 947655476108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655477979","data":{"timestamp":" 947655477979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655480217","data":{"timestamp":" 947655480217"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIZUILIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655482463","data":{"timestamp":" 947655482463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655485139","data":{"timestamp":" 947655485139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655486988","data":{"timestamp":" 947655486988"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655488925","data":{"timestamp":" 947655488924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655491027","data":{"timestamp":" 947655491027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655492684","data":{"timestamp":" 947655492684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kofia yangu ilizuiliwa katika matawi ya mti wa miiba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIIBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655495368","data":{"timestamp":" 947655495368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655497994","data":{"timestamp":" 947655497994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nililia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655499806","data":{"timestamp":" 947655499806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655501824","data":{"timestamp":" 947655501824"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655504066","data":{"timestamp":" 947655504066"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655506273","data":{"timestamp":" 947655506273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655506355","data":{"timestamp":" 947655506355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 5e8dc983-a569-4088-979f-dd9103be11c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na sikula chakula changu cha jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655515317","data":{"timestamp":" 947655515317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655515551","data":{"timestamp":" 947655515550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655516525","data":{"timestamp":" 947655516524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655517810","data":{"timestamp":" 947655517809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655520757","data":{"timestamp":" 947655520756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655521612","data":{"timestamp":" 947655521611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655521932","data":{"timestamp":" 947655521932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655523175","data":{"timestamp":" 947655523175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655526741","data":{"timestamp":" 947655526741"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655527734","data":{"timestamp":" 947655527733"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655527994","data":{"timestamp":" 947655527994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655528955","data":{"timestamp":" 947655528955"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655531877","data":{"timestamp":" 947655531877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655532919","data":{"timestamp":" 947655532918"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655533402","data":{"timestamp":" 947655533401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655537995","data":{"timestamp":" 947655537994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655538108","data":{"timestamp":" 947655538107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 2e209ed6-8912-47e4-a5d3-d593eeb72d2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655551472","data":{"timestamp":" 947655551471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 7b18a4fc-ca70-4fc4-aacd-eaa119ae9bf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655554392","data":{"timestamp":" 947655554392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 7b18a4fc-ca70-4fc4-aacd-eaa119ae9bf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655556613","data":{"timestamp":" 947655556613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 7b18a4fc-ca70-4fc4-aacd-eaa119ae9bf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655557314","data":{"timestamp":" 947655557314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 7b18a4fc-ca70-4fc4-aacd-eaa119ae9bf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947655557484","data":{"timestamp":" 947655557484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_081824"," gameId":" 7b18a4fc-ca70-4fc4-aacd-eaa119ae9bf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Palikuwa na basi moja tu katika kijiji cha Ebei."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}